ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: JP STEVENS
  - JP Stevens- Company Film. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Includes: contact sheets; film frames; (black) women and children
  - JP Stevens- Contract Ratification Victory October 1980. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Includes: auditorium cheering
  - JP Stevens- Corporate Campaign., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Includes: contact sheets; Seamens Bank 11/79; "youngest demonstrator"; Carpenters Union members joined the Park Ave. picket line; A. Giorini and F. Faverzani from Italy joined the Joint Council 13 Director F. Denovillis and Local 563B A. Pernicone on line
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/79., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Includes: boycott 11/79 Seamen's Bank; contact sheets
  - JP Stevens- Demos 11/30/78., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Includes: factory building; Wallace, NC factory; Roanoke Rapids factory; Rock Hill, SC plant; Roanoke Rapids demo; Allentown 11/30/78; PA, Jim Ritter; negatives; 11/30/78 Cleveland rally; Benny Bonanno 11/30/78; 11/30/78 Elaine Potter; 11/30/78 Max Amdur
  - JP Stevens- Demos 11/30/78., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Includes: Jim Laughten speaks Boston 11/29 Pedestrian mall; Baltimore demo 11/30; Toronto 11/30/78 Bud Clark leafletting; Miami 11/30/78 Rose Mary Reznicek, Ed Stevenson, Sarah Brown, Florence Kaplan, Don Resha, Sheron Dranow, Al Gonzalez; Miami 11/30/78
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Includes: Detroit 11/30/78 Wings of Truth Gospel Church Choir sang "We Shall Overcome"; Detroit 11/30/78 demo; Allentown 11/30/78 demo; Portland, OR 11/30/78 demo; Scranton 11/30/78 disabled man leads parade; Scranton, PA 11/30/78 demo; Ted Gatto, William
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Includes: Robert Hall employees receive checks, Bernard Firestone, David Chaney; Stevens boycott Phila.; Mrs. King at JPS demo; Alan Kistler Wash. Rally 11/30; Toronto 11/30/78; Claude Pepper, Ed Stephenson Miami 11/30/78; Phila 11/30/78 Harry Goldsmith,
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78. [folder 1 of 6], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Includes: contact sheets, photocopies, miscellaneous papers.
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78. [folder 2 of 6], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78. [folder 3 of 6], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78. [folder 4 of 6], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78. [folder 5 of 6], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - JP Stevens Demos 11/30/78. [folder 6 of 6], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - JP Stevens- Detroit., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Includes: 1978 boycott; rally 9/78 Detroit; Emma Henderson Detroit's Cobo Hall 11/30/78
  - JP Stevens Dublin, GA. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Includes: (black) singers; organizing committee members; (black) family; Georgia In-Plant Organizing School, Van Peavy speaks; contact sheets
  - JP Stevens (Rally) Edison, NJ. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Includes: rally; contact sheets
  - JP Stevens- Education Committee., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Includes: contact sheets 3/77
  - JP Stevens (Edwards, Joseph). (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Includes: man, family (black)
  - JP Stevens Georgia Boycott. (Box 13, Folder 26)
    Includes: misc. papers, photocopies
  - JP Stevens Georgia Boycott. (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Includes: Atlanta; Milledgeville; Rome, GA rally
  - JP Stevens Gimbels T-Shirt Bust. (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Includes: bust, contact sheets
  - JP Stevens- Great Falls. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    Includes: crowd outside ACTWU offices in Great Falls, SC. Contact sheets
  - JP Stevens- Knoxville, TN. (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Includes: Bill Troy, LeRoy Brandenburg, Bill Linge, Mae Smith, Stevens boycott
  - JP Stevens Little Rock., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Includes: 11/30/78 demo
  - JP Stevens (Los Angeles Dodgers). (Box 13, Folder 32)
    Includes: baseball game protest; press conferences
  - JP Stevens Mass Boycott., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Includes: Milwaukee 11/30/78; L. 590 Boston Big Business Day rally; Boston group outside Woolworths Eastern Hills Mall; Governor Joseph Brennan's announcement on JPS
  - JP Stevens Plants. (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Includes: Roanoke Rapids, NC; Roanoke Plant-2; midnight shift; Great Falls, SC; Charlotte, NC headquarters; contact sheets
  - JP Stevens Princeton Demo. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 35 Includes: Princeton demo
  - JP Stevens Rally 12/77., 1977 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 36 Includes: contact sheets
  - JP Stevens (Religion)., 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 37 Includes: 6/24/77 Community Awareness Meeting, Fernwood United Methodist Church; Reverend Dr. Jack Crum; Sister Jeanine Maynard; Father Patrick Sullivan and Reverend Bill Samplatsky-Jarman; To
  - JP Stevens (Roanoke Rapids, NC) 8/77 Congressional Hearings., 1977 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 38 Includes: testimony, contact sheets
  - JP Stevens Round-up. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 39 Includes: JPS Day Beaneston, AL; Finley speaks at Ohio State AFL-CIO meeting
  - JP Stevens (Seattle, WA). Boycott., 1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 40 Includes: 2/14/78 boycott march; auto mechanics help 2/14/78; the Little Bread Company; April 1st rally Seattle, WA. JPS and Auto Traders Strike; papers
  - JP Stevens Settlement 10/19/80 Folder#2 (dups and contacts). (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 41 Includes: contact sheets
  - JP Stevens Settlement 10/19/80 Folder #2 (dups and contacts). (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 42 Includes: victory JPS Roanoke Rapids; workers; ratification meeting
  - JP Stevens Shelby, NC. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 43 Includes: union committee organizing; contact sheets
  - JP Stevens Stockholder Meeting, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 44 Includes: contact sheets; stockholders meeting; workers, speeches; Jobholders meeting; Myrtle Cribbs, Harold McIver, Reverend Edward Fleming, Grady Collum, Sol Stetin, Danny Blackwell, Bennie
  - JP Stevens Master Photo File (Binder). (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 45 'Includes: photocopy of binder,
  - JP Stevens Master Photo File (Binder)., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 46 Includes: booth display 5/76; hearing from Rep. Frank Thompson, Myrtle Cribbs, Addie Jackson, Reverend Joseph Williams, Maurine Hedgepeth; 3/15/76 hearing: Harold McIver, Reverend Joseph Willi
- Series IV: LEAFLETING
  - Leafleting., 1962 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 47 Includes: 1962 Kann's, rabbits; "the White House" (store); 1962 The Grand Milwaukee, rabbits; rabbits, Shellenburg's 1962 Philadelphia; Adam, Meldrum, and Anderson Co.; F.R. Tripler and Co.; C
  - Leafleting., 1962-1963 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 48 Includes: 11/63 Beaumont, TX Beall's Dept. Store; rabbits at O'Nell's; Akron, Ohio George Burdon and rabbits of Akron Labor Council Ladies Auxiliary; Pittsburgh 1963 11/62 old man leafleting
  - Leafleting., 1964 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 49 Includes: Black woman leafleting to Black family; leafleting 1/64-2/64 Baltimore, MD; St. Louis 1/64 L. 84; L. 17 1/64 St. Louis; Los Angeles 1/64; 1/64 McKeesport, PA; Cleveland 1/64; Akron,
  - Leafleting., 1964 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 50 Includes: Masters, NY, 3/64; Adam Hats; Carlton Men's Shops; L. 17 at Britt's St. Louis
  - Leafleting., 1964 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 51 Includes: Adam Hats, Connecticut, UAW L. 987; Hat Workers L. 120 Newark, NJ; New Departure Company Meriden, Conn. L. 987; Art's Men's Shop Chicago, Ill.; Hartford, CT 1964; Texas Miller leafle
  - Leafleting., 1949-1964 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 13, ff 52 Includes: Montreal 2/2/49 group feeding pig; J.C. Rich 8th Convention; Al Rose distributing leaflets, NY 11/63; Al Rose and James McNamara; Harry Fromkin leafleting in Pittsburgh, 11/63; 7/64
- Series V: MISCELLANEOUS OVERSIZED
  - Stevens Worker-Great Falls: Union Wins Plant Safety (Box 43, Folder 19)
    This was loose in box 13, collection was re-organized
  - J.P. Stevens - Misc. (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - "The Struggle for Economic Justice at J.P. Stevens" (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - "Justice vs. J.P. Stevens" (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - "Testimony: A documentary filmJustice vs. J.P. Stevens" (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - "ACTWU: Media Information Kit" (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Panorama: AFL-CIO 100th Anniversary Convention NYC, NY 11/16/81; 1st Annual Dinner Israel Forbinan Shop 12/5/36, 1936-1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ACTWU., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 1a)
    Includes: 20th Anniversary Simon Scholarships 1984
  - ACWA- Conventions- 50th. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes: speech, crowd
  - Ad Campaigns- misc., 1917 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Includes: 3/9/17 Advance: Farah Company; Mrs. Roosevelt; Ellis Island
  - AFL-CIO., 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Includes: 11/15/79; 11/19/79; Meany's Funeral St. Matthews 1/15/80
  - Amalgamated Housing New York and Chicago., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Includes: buildings, Harper Square, Chicago 12/11/71
  - American Textile Manufacturers Institute. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Includes: opening; spinning; warping; dyeing; weaving; knitting; screen printing; finishing; inspecting; research
  - Harriman, Averell., 1956 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Includes: 9th Convention 1956 tosses his hat into the ring
  - Hatters Convention., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Includes: 6/59 GEB 10th Convention
  - Hatters General Executive Board., 1948-1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Includes: 1/26-3/1/48 Atlantic City, NJ; 3/46 Atlantic City, NJ; 65th Birthday Party James Novaco Traymore Hotel, 6/17/54 Atlantic City, NJ
  - Imports. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Includes: Canadian textile marches; VanHeusen shirt marches; "wages not welfare" march
  - Misc. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Includes: speech; music; Yiddish Theater; group shot w/ priest
  - NY Millinery Jt. Bd., 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Includes: Juno Lighting, Des Plaines, IL, literacy class; 2/62 District Meeting-Hotel Diplomat; signing CB Agreement 1/63 Hotel Astor; NY Millinery Strike 12/62; NY Jt. Bd. Dinner 12/28/67
  - Shops. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Includes: contact sheets; "Arrow" shirt plant; misc.
  - Strikes. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Includes: HIS apparel; National News
  - Union Label., 1947 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Includes: NYC 2/17-8/47 Union Label Promotion Conference delegates Men's Hat and Cap Locals
  - United Hatters., 1936-1956 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Includes: GEB 6/2/56; GEB 6/18/54; GEB 1/13/50; GEB 6/13-6/18 1949; International Board of United Hatters 10/12/36